all right time to welcome our marus
guest Shashi Krishan of beras and life
insurance now joins in Sashi hi good
morning good to have you on the show uh
does it look like the shallow correction
is over the market is back to winning
way and what's the best way to play this
market now I think the Market's moving
into a consolidation phase uh and uh uh
you know if you go away from the Nifty a
lot of the stocks are actually corrected
quite significantly and therefore there
is opportunity in this market but think
uh uh a couple of things actually been
uh in favor of us you know one uh is the
fact that uh uh you know interest rates
clearly The View on interest rates
clearly is that interest rates will
soften uh you know over the next couple
of months uh whether policy rates will
get cut immediately in December or they
will get cut in February is a I mean is
a matter of uh sort of debate and we
would have to take a call on how the RBI
looks at it but I think a lot of things
are going right on uh you know on the
interest rate front and we do believe
believe that interest rates will soften
quite significantly uh which is I think
good news on a large number of fronts
one uh uh the fact that uh lower
interest rates is uh you know is very
good for the investment cycle and you
see the investment cycle returning much
quickly uh secondly I think it's going
to have a very very positive impact on
both the current account deficit and the
fiscal deficit so if you look at the
fiscal deficit for example you know
lower interest rates broadly coupled
with the fact that you've got low lower
oil prices would mean that you would
land up with something like a 4 and a
half% fiscal deficit for the current
year you could actually even land up
with uh you know a current account
deficit of something like you know
around two so a lot of these virtuous
The Virtuous cycle seems to be coming
back which I think is good news uh and
therefore you know uh the markets did
seem to take a pause but uh my own fear
is that you know there will be interest
that will return into interest rates
sensitives and cyclicals uh you know
over the next couple of months which
will sort of bring the market you know
back into you know momentum okay uh Mr
chrishan how would you how would you
position yourself in the banking space
now so clearly we are taking a view that
interest rates will come down and
interest rates coming down is in our
opinion very positive for the uh the
banking sector and therefore we are
incrementally buying into the banking
sector both into the private Banks and
into the government owned Banks uh in
fact the state owned Banks got
significantly beaten down uh you know
given the fact that U you know people
had concerns on asset quality in fact if
you look at this quarter asset quality
say still seems to be a concern I mean
if you look at some of the results that
have come out it's not that asset
quality worries have gone out completely
but if it interest rates come down
significantly I think uh what will
typically happen is that uh you know it
becomes uh you know an up up cycle for
all these Banks and you will see
improving asset qualities over the next
couple of quarters so we are taking
exposure into you know the banking
sector both the state owned Banks and
the uh private Banks Frontline it has
corrected 12 to 15% in certain cases
even higher than that good time to get
some of the stocks back in portfolio or
would you wait for more correction I
think uh if you look at uh the the
immediate correction it has been because
of the uh the this quarter results I
mean uh except for infosis which sort of
was more or less in uh line with
consensus estimates uh most of the rest
of the it results seem to have
disappointed marginally and that's one
of the reasons why it is corrected but
one of the reasons why you know this
disappointment was there was I suspect
because uh there was OV expectation in
terms of what they could deliver uh the
other problem is that we are seeing a
Slowdown in the global economy I mean we
are seeing you know uh in recent times
both Europe and to some extent Japan
slowing down quite significantly and
that obviously this is going to impact
some bit of Outsourcing but I think you
know value will start coming back into
the it after these kind of Correction
you know with a 15% correction some of
the stock prices you will see value
coming back because the long-term story
Still Remains intact and you know as an
Outsourcing destination I think India
still has got tremendous potential so
whereas we haven't uh reduced our
exposure significantly we have not be
increasing exposure we will wait for
opportunity to get in okay I wanted to
ask you about the Telecom space uh do
you have a view in terms of a couple of
these telecom stocks say such as the
parti and the ideas and the Reliance
Communications of the world and any sort
of incremental exposure that you've
increased or what would be it be as a
total uh percentage of your portfolio so
if you look at this quarter results I
think there is only one result that has
come and that has been you know more or
less in term better than consensus uh so
we haven't seen too much uh else coming
out of the space in this quarter but
having said that I think there is still
lack of clarity in terms of you know
Spectrum auctions and the availability
of spectrum and I think we will need
some clarity and I think as we go
forward as more and more of these policy
decisions take uh I mean you know happen
we will see some clarity happening in
that space uh but at the end of the day
I think that is one uh you know play on
the domestic Market that you cannot miss
out on because in my opinion uh a lot of
interest in the market has uh shifted
out of typically what were export plays
into domestic plays and as the interest
shifts back into domestic place I think
the Telecom space is one space you
cannot ignore midcap infra that the you
know stocks have doubled or in certain
cases trebled this year they had a bit
of consolidation but back to winning
spring now how would you approach that
yeah so if you look at the midcap space
as a whole I think uh you know there was
a significant runup and after a
significant run up I mean people I mean
all of us in the market tend to believe
that they were overvalued and therefore
you know they paused some of them
corrected but uh if you ask me I'd still
look at you know many of the uh cyclical
in the midcap space that are you know
where the quality of earnings is good
because it is these signal that will you
know react immediately once the
investment cycle sort of uh turns around
and you know if you could identify good
quality midcaps that are plays on the
Revival of the investment cycle I think
that's why you would be able to make uh
money in the mid midcap space okay if
you have to put in fresh money and you
say you add 100 rupees how much would
you allocate to the frontliners at this
point in time how much would you
allocate to the midcaps for incremental
returns from current levels so given the
fact that uh we manage Insurance funds
and uh I mean a large part of the
mandates that we have are basically you
know to get into lower risk um Equity
Investments much of our asset allocation
is into the into the larger caps right
into the into the larger caps and
therefore you know uh we we still uh you
know are looking very seriously at the
Pharma sector we are still looking very
seriously at the banking sector where we
see value and opportunity but that is
not to say that we will not put my put
money into the midcap space I told you
good quality midcaps are ultimately
going to be the large caps of the future
and therefore I mean we have about 20%
of our portfolio actually allocated to
uh you know midcaps at this point of
time okay fair enough all right so we
leave it to that thank you very much for
joining in and taking us through your
fundamental View